myassurantpolicy.com 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Assurant

If You are an individual consumer located in California or other applicable state (if any), this notice is given to You pursuant to state law. It addresses personally identifiable information collected by Us about You when You visit or use this Site. 

Assurant Specialty Property and its affiliated companies are committed to protecting the personal information entrusted to us by consumers who visit our website. The trust you place in us when you share personal information and/or the personal information of another person or entity is a responsibility we take very seriously and is the cornerstone of how we conduct our business.

We use the brand name "Assurant Specialty Property" to associate our products and services and to connect us with the brand of our parent company, Assurant, Inc. This Policy is intended to inform our consumers of our practices with regard to consumers' personal information collected through this website. As used in this online Privacy Policy, the term "you and your" are defined to include all website visitors including, but not limited to, customers, brokers, third party administrators, and/or representatives of any of the above.

**I. Categories of personal information we collect**

The term "personal information" includes any individually identifiable information about you that we collect online, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, or social security number. We collect this information when you voluntarily disclose it to us in connection with a service offered on this website. Our website has security safeguards that are designed to protect any personal information that you decide to give us via this website. You may, however, choose not to provide this information and use an alternative form of communication such as telephone, fax, or regular mail. By using our website your consent to this online Privacy Policy is implied.

**II. How we use and disclose personal information**

If you choose to provide us with personal information, such as in an email to one of our online email boxes, by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it to us through our website or by logging onto our website, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us provide you with the information you have requested. We also need information from you when you register for online access to your claims information. We use that information in order to process transactions that you request and to authenticate you as a registered user.

We do not sell or rent personal information about visitors to this site or consumers who use the site. We will use and disclose the information you give us only as required or permitted by law. This may include, for example, disclosures to third parties that perform business services on our behalf or in response to a request from a law enforcement agency or subpoena.

**III. How we collect and use personal information**

Personally-identifiable information is information that allows us to identify you. We collect, analyze, monitor online activities, and store any personal information that you voluntarily provide by sending us an email to one of our online email boxes, by filling out a form with personal information and submitting through our website or by logging onto our website.

This information helps us assist you with technical issues encountered when using our website, improve our website and make your visits more appealing. You may choose not to provide personal information to us by not sending us an email using our online email boxes, by not filling out a form with personal information and by not logging onto our website. Refer to Section XIII for other ways to contact us.

**IV. How we collect and use non-personal information**

Non-personal information is generic data that does not allow us to identify or contact a specific individual. We look at such data on an individual and collective basis, to help us detect trends that might help us to improve our website.

We may gather generic data automatically from your web browser, such as: the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; the Uniform Resource Locator (URL) click path to, through, and from our website; and the date and time you access our website.

**V. Email communication**

To protect your privacy, please do not use email to communicate information to us that you consider confidential. Email is not a secure method of communication and is not encrypted. Accordingly, an email message potentially could be accessed and viewed by others without your knowledge and/or permission, while in transit to us.

**VI. Cookies**

Persistent cookies may be used on this website. These are pieces of information or data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. We use this information to analyze traffic patterns and improve our website. If you prefer not to accept cookies, the help portion of the toolbar on most web browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, disabling cookies may result in certain parts of the website not operating correctly or prevent you from taking full advantage of some of the features of our website.

**VII. "Do Not Track" signals**

We do not respond to a web browser’s “do not track” signal or other mechanisms that signal a request that our site not track the consumer’s online activities over time and across websites.

Other parties may collect personally identifiable information about consumer’s online activities over time and across different websites when a consumer uses our website or service.

**VIII. Process for reviewing or requesting changes to personal information**

If you think that any personal information we have collected about you is inaccurate, you may send a written request for review to us at the address provided in Section XIII. We will investigate your request and make appropriate changes if warranted.

**IX. Changes to this policy**

We may change this Policy from time to time without notice. The most current Policy will be posted on this website. You should therefore review this online Privacy Policy regularly.

**X. Effective date**

Effective Date: February 14, 2006 /as amended December 2013.

**XI. Links to other Websites**

This website may contain links to other websites that may have online information practices different from ours. We are not responsible for the privacy and security practices of those websites, and we encourage our visitors to learn about the privacy and security practices of those websites.

**XII. Children**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13. For more information about protecting your child's privacy online, visit the Federal Trade Commission.

**XIII. Privacy contact information**

We welcome your questions or comments regarding this online Privacy Policy. Please write to The Assurant Solutions/Assurant Specialty Property Privacy Office, Post Office Box 979047, Miami, FL 33197-9047 or e-mail us your question at [theprivacyoffice@assurant.com](mailto:theprivacyoffice@assurant.com).
